Contact

samriddhabasu1234@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/samriddhabasu-4594401ba (LinkedIn) linktr.ee/Samriddha_Basu (Other)

Top Skills

English
C (Programming Language)
Java

Samriddha Basu

|| Campus Business Manager at PrepBytes || PR Head at GFG SRM NCR Students' Chapter || PR jr. Lead at CSI SRM NCR Students' Chapter ||

New Delhi

Summary

A sophomore pursuing B.Tech in CSE with specialisation in Cloud Computing at SRM IST Delhi-NCR Campus. I'm an ardent technophile and a workhorse, I love connecting with people and having a network of like-minded people. I'm pretty well in presenting and speaking in public. I have a good command on C/C++(5star in HackerRank) and Java and trying my hands on Android Development using Kotlin. I stick to a task until it gets done perfectly (which I think I should be both be proud of and be not proud of). I currently am the jr. PR Lead at CSI SRM NCR Chapter, PR Head at GFG SRM NCR Chapter and CBM at PrepBytes of my Campus. Public Relations and Tech have been my domain since my freshman days and hope to explore other domains too. I am a quick learner and can adapt to changes real quick. My short term goal as of now is to master Android Development and become a good orator. I'm a team player and can lead a team from front. I believe in wise work and staying loyal to the organisation I'm in.

Experience

PrepBytes
Campus Business Manager
December 2021 - Present (2 months)
Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh, India

Computer Society of India (CSI) - SRM NCR 1 year

P.R. Lead jr. at Computer Society of India (CSI) - SRM NCR April 2021 - Present (10 months)

Modinagar, Uttar Pradesh, India

Member of Students Council February 2021 - April 2021 (3 months) India

GeeksforGeeks
Public Relations Officer
December 2021 - Present (2 months)

Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh, India

Education

SRM University (Sri Ramaswamy Memorial University)

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Engineering · (2020 - 2024)